<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Better Humanoid Mechanoid</name>
	<author>CannonedMutton</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Better.Humanoid.Mechanoid.CN</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	</loadAfter>

	<description>I have made a series of humanoid robots, which have higher skill levels and stronger weapons. In addition, there is a map switch between the conscription version and the non-conscription version, so that you can see their lovely faces in daily life and their handsome armor in battle

This update includes four mechdroids: mechanical centipede, mechanical nurse, mechanical swordsman and mechanical maid, as well as new secondary core and cultivation buildings.

They have more powerful weapons, more efficient performance, and the ability to carry, clean, and craft.

A series of mechdroids, such as mechanic, mechanical sniper, mechanical commander and mechanical reload soldier, will be updated in the future

我制作了一系列人形机器人，她们有着更高的技能等级以及更加强力的武器，此外还有着征召版与非征召版的贴图切换，可以让大家在日常生活看到她们可爱面庞的同时，也可以在战斗中看到她们的帅气装甲。
本次更新有机械蜈蚣、机械护士、机械剑士以及机械女仆四个机械体，还有全新的次级核心、培育建筑。她们有着更加强力的武器，更高效的性能，以及搬运、清扫、制作等能力
日后还会更新机械技师、机械狙击手、机械指挥官以及机械重装战士等一系列机械体，敬请期待。
该模组支持CE，支持枪火mod。

Я сделал серию человекоподобных роботов, которые имеют более высокий уровень навыков и более мощное оружие. Кроме того, есть переключение карт между призывной и не призывной версиями, чтобы вы могли видеть их милые лица в повседневной жизни и их красивую броню в бою.

Это обновление включает в себя четырех мехдроидов: механическую многоножку, механическую медсестру, механического фехтовальщика и механическую горничную, а также новое вторичное ядро ​​и постройки для выращивания.

У них более мощное оружие, более эффективная работа и возможность носить, чистить и создавать.

Серия мехдроидов, таких как механик, механический снайпер, механический командир и механический солдат-перезарядка, будет обновлена ​​в будущем.

感谢@ Caren Hortensia 提供的俄语语言包，同时欢迎其他国家的朋友提供该MOD的其他语言包，我将会把您一同放在作者一栏中，并优先提供我所创作的其他MOD的抢先体验版
Thanks to @Caren Hortensia for providing the Russian language pack, and friends from other countries are welcome to provide other language packs of this MOD. I will put you in the author column and give priority to the early access version of other MODs I created

	  </description>
</ModMetaData>